export const Jeopardy = [
  [
    'Who Said It',
    'Finish The Line',
    'Dwight Schrute',
    'Food and Drink',
    'Michael Scott',
    'Minor Characters',
  ],
  {
    question: 'Dr. Tuna, MD, I have some terrible news.',
    answer: 'Andy Bernard',
    answered: false,
    value: 200,
  },
  {
    question: 'I declare __________',
    answer: 'Bankruptcy',
    answered: false,
    value: 200,
  },
  {
    question: 'What kind of bear is best?',
    answer: 'Black bear',
    answered: false,
    value: 200,
  },
  {
    question: 'What was Michael cooking when he burned his foot?',
    answer: 'Bacon',
    answered: false,
    value: 200,
  },
  {
    question:
      'At corporate, what was Michael\'s message asked to be sent to Jan?',
    answer: '<motor boat noise>',
    answered: false,
    value: 200,
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the woman that Michael was fond of while in Canada?',
    answer: 'Concierge Marie',
    answered: false,
    value: 200,
  },

  {
    question: 'I’m not gonna start doubting my drunken self now',
    answer: 'Robert California',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question: 'You ever notice you can only ooze two things? _________ ___ ___',
    answer: 'Sexuality and pus',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What was the theme of the room Jim and Pam stay in at Schrute Farms?',
    answer: 'Irrigation',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the name of the good pizza place?',
    answer: 'Alfredo\'s Pizza Cafe',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question: 'How many points were in Michael\'s plan to save the company?',
    answer: '45',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question: 'Which warehouse worker was once a heart surgeon?',
    answer: 'Hidetoshi Hasagawa',
    answered: false,
    value: 400,
  },
  {
    question:
      'I don’t think Michael’s ever done drugs. I don’t know if anyone has ever offered him any.',
    answer: 'Ryan Howard',
    answered: false,
    value: 600,
  },
  {
    question: 'Sitting in my office with a _____ __ _______ _____',
    answer: 'plate of grilled bacon',
    answered: false,
    value: 600,
  },
  {
    question: 'How much did Jim spend on his Dwight constume?',
    answer: '$11',
    answered: false,
    value: 600,
  },
  {
    question: 'What Chinese thing did Andy eat at Gabe’s?',
    answer: 'Powdered seahorse',
    answered: false,
    value: 600,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What did Michael do to be able to tell his and Andy\'s "girlfriends" apart?',
    answer: 'He marked her arm',
    answered: false,
    value: 600,
    dailyDouble: true,
  },
  {
    question: 'How did Creed "know" the CPR trainer?',
    answer: 'He saw her in the parking lot',
    answered: false,
    value: 600,
  },
  {
    question:
      'I saw it. I saw it, and it was amazing! Who said I didn’t see it?',
    answer: 'Pam Beesley',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question:
      'The tea in Nepal is very hot. ___ ___ ______ __ ____ __ ____ ______',
    answer: 'But the coffee in Peru is much hotter.',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question: 'What surgery does Dwight have in Florida?',
    answer: 'Appendectomy',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question: 'What kind of beer was being advertised on Michael\'s neon sign?',
    answer: 'St. Pauli Girl',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What song did Michael and Dwight end up singing in a cementery in the "Chair Model" episode?',
    answer: 'American Pie',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the food truck owner that remembered Toby but not Jim?',
    answer: 'Ernesto',
    answered: false,
    value: 800,
  },
  {
    question: 'Me love you long tim. Me lobe yoy long time.',
    answer: 'Harvey the Computer',
    answered: false,
    value: 1000,
  },
  {
    question:
      'The boat was actually Plan C. The Church was plan B and ___ _ ___ ________ ___ _ ____, ____ ____ ___',
    answer: 'Plan A was marrying her a long, long time ago',
    answered: false,
    value: 1000,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What was Dwight\'s yearly salary as a co-owner of a B&B with Satan?',
    answer: '$80,000',
    answered: false,
    value: 1000,
  },
  {
    question: 'What brand of chips did Karen have trouble finding in Stamford?',
    answer: 'Herr\'s',
    answered: false,
    value: 1000,
  },
  {
    question:
      'How fast did Michael think he ran according to the speedometer outside the office?',
    answer: '31 mph',
    answered: false,
    value: 1000,
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of Jim and Pam\'s actor friend that played "Asian Jim"?',
    answer: 'Steve',
    answered: false,
    value: 1000,
  },
];
